《迷失》前情提要
Previously on "Lost"
我来是要告诉你
I'm here to tell you
那岛不可能 只让你一个人回去
That the island won't Let you come alone.
你们所有人都要回去
All of you have to go back.
你来就说这个吗
Is that what this is about?
太离谱了  你们全疯了
This is insane. You guys are crazy.
- Kate - Jack  别说了
- Kate - Jack, don't!
- Sayid  你要去哪儿  -我再也不想跟你们掺和了
- Sayid, where are you going? - I don't want any part of this.
Jin还在上面
It's Jin!
-你怎么知道他没死  -有人知道
- How do you know he's alive?! - There's someone...
那人就在洛杉矶
Someone here in Los Angeles.
什么人  是谁
Someone? who?
准备告诉我们
The same person that's gonna show us
如何回到岛上的那个人
How to get back to the island.
救命
Help!
有人吗
Anyone!
救命
Help!
救命  Jack
Help, jack!
救命  有人吗
Help! anyone!
救命
Help!
救救我
救命
Help!
-没事的   -天啊
It's okay. You're okay. Relax. Aah! Oh, god!
我的天啊
Oh, god!
好吧
Okay.
-天啊    -我们能站起来了
- Oh, my god! - We can stand.
什么
- What?
上帝啊
Oh, my god.
真的发生了
It really happened.
Kate
Kate.
Kate  你能听见我说话吗
Kate, can you hear me?
Jack
Jack?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我们这是...
Are we...
对
Yeah.
我们回来了
We're back.
发生什么了
What happened?
46小时前
46 Hours Earlier
我记得我说的是一个都不能少
I thought I said all of them.
这么短时间  只能找到这么多人
This is all I could get on short notice.
我看现在就得开始了
Guess it'll have to do for now.
好吧  咱们开始吧
All right. Let's get started.
准备好了吗
Shall we?
这是什么地方
What is this place?
达摩组织管这里叫灯塔站
The dharma initiative called it the lamp post.
他们就是从这里找到的小岛
This is how they found the island.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视原创翻译制作
最新最快的美剧 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译： 娜姬雅911  宝宝宝  blackeyepea  rosemaryai
时间轴：  雨中泪  字幕总监：七色九天  非燕
■
后期： 梁良   校对：  许愿
你知道这个地方吗
Did you know about this place?
不知道
No.
我不知道
No, I didn't.
他说的是真话吗
Is he telling the truth?
很可能是说谎
Probably not.
开始吧
Here we go.
好吧
All right.
如果这让你们不知所措  我很抱歉  但是
I apologize if this is confusing, but...
让我们集中精神  好吗
Let's pay attention, yes?
我们现在所处的房间  建造于多年之前
The room we're standing in was constructed years ago
有无可匹敌的大量磁能量经过这里
Over a unique pocket of electromagnetic energy.
这些磁场与全世界其它类似的磁场相连接
That energy connects to similar pockets all over the world.
然而建造这所房间的人
The people who built this room, however,
-只对一件事感兴趣  -是那个岛吧
- Were only interested in one. - The island.
对  就是那个岛
Yes. the island.
他们搜集的证据都证明了此岛的存在
They'd gathered proof that it existed.
他们确定它就在某地
They knew it was out there somewhere,
但就是找不到具体地点
But they just couldn't find it.
后来有位很聪明的家伙建造了这个钟摆
Then a very clever fellow built this pendulum
他的理论是  人们应该
On the theoretical notion that they should stop looking
停止揣测小岛可能在哪里
For where the island was supposed to be
而转向研究它要去哪里
And start looking for where it was going to be.
你说的"去哪里"是什么意思
What do you mean, "where it was going to be"?
这个人的假设是正确的
Well, this fellow presumed, and correctly,
已经证明 这个岛在移动
as it turned out, That the island was always moving.
要不怎么人们老也搜救不到你们
Why do you think you were never rescued?
虽然这个岛的移动  看似随机
Now while the movements of the island seem random,
但是这人和他的研究组
This man and his team
还是创制出了一个方程组
created a series of equations
这个方程组准确度极高
Which tell us,
它能预言
With a high degree of probability,
该岛会在哪个时刻  运动到 哪个地点
Where it is going to be at a certain point... In time.
如果说它是扇窗户
Windows, as it were,
那么当它开着的时候  人们就能出去再回来
That while open, provide a route back.
很可惜 这扇窗户开不了太长时间
Unfortunately, These windows don't stay open for very long.
你们的窗户 36小时之后就关上了
Yours closes... In 36 hours.
不好意思  打断一下
Um, I'm sorry. excuse me.
我怎么听不明白
Am I really hearing this?
这说的都是什么啊
That's what this is about?
你们愿意回到小岛上吗  自愿的吗
You're all going back to the island willingly?
是的  Desmond  你来这儿干吗
Yes. why are you here, desmond?
我是来传口信儿的
I came here to deliver a message.
你儿子Daniel Faraday 让我来的
Daniel Faraday Your son-- Sent me here.
他想让我告诉你
He wanted me to tell you
他和岛上所有的人  都需要你的帮助
That he and all the people on the island need your help.
他说  只有你才能帮他们
He said that only you could help them.
他说的不是Jack  不是Sun  不是Ben
He didn't say Jack. He didn't say Sun. He didn't say Ben.
-他只说了你  -但是我正在帮忙  亲爱的
- He said you. - But I am helping, dear.
口信儿传完了
Consider the message delivered.
很遗憾地告诉你  Desmond
I'm sorry to have to tell you this, desmond,
你跟这个岛的事儿  还没了断呢
But the island isn't done with you yet.
这个女人浪费我人生中4年的时间
This woman cost me four years of my life--
一去不复返的4年啊  就因为你跟我说
Four years that I'll never get back because you told me
说我应该回到那个岛上去
That I was supposed to go to the island!
说那才是我该死归宿
That it was my bloody purpose!
你听好了  老兄  你仔仔细细听好了
You listen to me, brother, and you listen carefully.
这些人  他们不过是在利用咱们
These people-- they're just usin' us.
他们跟咱们玩猫腻 而我们只是筹码
They're playing some kind of game, And we are just the pieces.
无论她让你干什么
Whatever she tells you to do...
当她放屁
Ignore it.
你是不是说那岛跟我还没完了
You say the island's not done with me?
我告诉你  我跟这岛彻底玩完
Well, I'm done with the island.
Jack
Jack...
你手里这个文件夹
The binder in your hands
所有的航线都飞过一些坐标
Shows all the air routes that fly over the coordinates
我相信那个岛  就在那些坐标上
Where I believe the island will be
从现在开始  有一天多的时间
In little more than a day from now.
有一班商务机从洛杉矶飞往关岛
There's a commercial airliner flying from l.a. to Guam.
它将飞过你们的窗户
It's going to go right through your window.
Ajira航空公司的3-1-6航班
Ajira Airways, flight 3-1-6.
如果希望小岛把你们带回去
Is you have any hope of the island bringing you back,
那就一定要坐这趟航班
It must be that plane.
你们所有人都要上飞机
You all need to be on it.
一定是这班才可以
It must be that flight.
如果你们 想要返回的话
If you... Want to return,
你们必须尽量重现
You need to recreate as best you can
与首次前往时
The circumstances
相同的环境
That brought you there in the first place
也就是说  当初谁跟你一块儿回来
That means as many of the same people
谁就跟你一块儿回去
As you are able to bring with you.
如果我们没办法说服其他人怎么办
And what if we can't get anyone else to come with us?
如果只有这几个呢
What if we're it?
我只能告诉你  结果... 难以预测
All I can tell you is the result would be... Unpredictable.
就这样吗
So that's it?
我们只要登上那班飞机
We just get on that flight,
然后祈祷那样行得通
And we just hope that it works?
就够了吗
That's all?
不  还不够  Jack
No, that's not all, jack...
至少对你来说不够
At least, not for you.
进来吧
Come on in.
Ben和Sun
Ben and sun--
只是得知了份内的事 这跟他们无关
Heard what they needed to hear, And this does not concern them.
找到了
Oh. here we are.
这是什么
What's this?
是John Locke的遗书
It's john locke's suicide note.
我... 我不知道
Uh... I, uh... I didn't know.
你怎么会知道
Well, why would you?
讣告中不适合 提到人们上吊之类的事情  Jack
Obituaries don't see fit To mention when people hang themselves, jack.
他为什么要自杀
Why would he kill himself?
我相信  有很多原因
There are many reasons, I'm sure,
但唯一紧要的是...
But the only one that matters is this--
他想帮助你们回去
He is going to help you get back.
John要做代理人
John is going to be a proxy.
代替者
A substitute.
谁的代替者
A substitute for who?
Jack
Jack...
你觉得是谁
Who do you think?
你要竭尽所能的 重现之前那趟航班上的环境
You need to, as best you can, Recreate the conditions of the original flight...
所以你需要 给John一些你父亲的东西
Which is why you need to Give john something of your father's.
你要找到一些属于你父亲的东西
You have to get something that belonged to your father,
然后交给John
And you need to give it to john.
什么
What?
这就是你的当务之急
That's what you have to do.
我父亲... 去世了
My father... Is gone.
我父亲三年前就死了
My father has been dead for three years.
你要我去...
You want me to...
然后交给Locke  他都进棺材了
A-and to give it to locke?! he's in a coffin!
这太荒谬了
This is ridiculous.
别去管这有多荒谬
Oh, stop thinking how ridiculous it is
扪心自问
And start asking yourself
你到底信不信这能行得通
Whether or not you believe it's going to work.
这就称之为天降奇迹  Jack
That's why it's called a leap of faith, jack.
Sun在哪
Where's sun?
她走了
She left.
Locke呢
And locke?
我是说...他的尸体呢  灵柩呢
I mean... his body? the coffin?
我让一个朋友照看它
I have a friend looking after it.
去机场的路上我去取
I'll pick it up on my way to the airport.
-Jack  她跟你说了什么  -没什么
- What did she say to you, jack? - nothing that matters.
她是谁
Who is she?
她为什么要...帮助我们
Why is she... helping us?
她怎么会知道这一切
How does she know all this?
圣徒多马
Thomas the apostle
当耶稣想回到犹太时
When jesus wanted to return to judea,
在得知他可能会在当地被谋杀后
Knowing that he would probably be murdered there,
多马对其他人说
Thomas said to the others,
"让我们随之而去吧  我们则与之同亡"
"let us also go, that we might die with him."
但多马并未因此出名
But thomas was not remembered for this bravery.
而是由于随后的
His claim to fame came later...
拒绝承认转世重生的理论
When he refused to acknowledge the resurrection.
他就是无法认同这种想法
He just couldn't wrap his mind around it.
故事似曾相识
The story goes...
他不得不触碰耶稣的伤口
That he needed to touch jesus' wounds
来说服自己
To be convinced.
他做到了吗
So was he?
当然做到了
Of course he was.
我们迟早都要被说服的  Jack
We're all convinced sooner or later, jack.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我答应过一个老朋友
Oh, I made a promise to an old friend of mine--
只是一些琐碎事情要处理
Just a loose end that needs tying up.
机场见  Jack
See you at the airport, jack.
你好
Hello?
对  就是我
Yeah, this is him.
他怎么了
He did what?
这是他第四次逃跑了
This is the fourth time he's left.
他必须要遵守规定
He's gotta follow the rules,
否则就要被转到全天候监视区
Or he'll have to move to our fully assisted facility.
是  我知道
Yeah, I understand.
现在  女士们  先生们
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
这就是我胆小的兔子
Here is my fraidy-cat rabbit!
你好  Ray
Hey, ray.
-你好  Jack  -下面
- Hey, jack. - As for my next trick,
我需要有人挑选一张卡片
I need someone to pick a card.
-想离开这里吗  -求之不得
- Wanna get out of here? - The sooner the better.
请选一张  看一看
Would you please pick one? look at it. mm-hmm.
你能告诉我这次为什么离开吗  Ray
You wanna tell me why you took off this time, ray?
我还需要回答吗
Do I really need to answer that?
至少告诉我你打算去哪儿
Will you at least tell me where the bus was headed?
无所谓
Doesn't matter.
去哪儿也比这儿强
Anywhere I go is somewhere better than here.
-你还打了包吗  -当然
- You packed a bag? - of course I did.
之前有一次  我其实已经成功逃脱了
One of these times, I'm actually gonna get away.
他们也无法找到我
They won't ever find me either.
再这样的话  他们就要把你赶出去了  Ray
Take off again, they're gonna throw you outta here, ray.
但是不做这个  我该干什么
But what would I do without my magic shows?
我来帮你把东西拿出来  爷爷
Let me help you unpack, granddad.
你好吗  孩子
So how are you, kiddo?
遇见真命天女了吗
You seeing anyone special?
你那次
Whatever happened
带来的那个女孩怎么样了
To the girl that you brought by with you that time?
就是那位满脸雀斑的美女
The pretty one with all the freckles?
她叫什么
What was her name?
Kate
Kate.
我们没在一起了
We're not together anymore.
好吧  乐观一点
Well, look at the bright side--
多来看看我
More time to come visit me.
我会的  爷爷  放心吧  但是...
I'd love to, granddad. I really would, but...
我想我或许...
I think I might be...
或许会离开一阵子
Might be going away for a while.
"离开"是去哪里
Where's "away" exactly?
比这儿好的地方
Somewhere better than here.
说的好
touche.
这些是你的吗  爷爷
Are these yours, granddad?
不
No.
那些是你父亲的
Those were your father's.
他死后  你妈妈寄给我一包他的遗物
Your mom sent me a box of his stuff after he died.
一定是我急于逃走给弄混了
Must've got mixed in when I packed for a quick getaway.
那些鞋子
These shoes...
我可以带走吗
Can I take them?
可以
Be my guest.
Kate
Kate?
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
你还打算回岛上去吗
Are you still going back to the island?
是的
Yeah.
是的  我想我要回去的
Yeah, I think I am.
那我和你一起走
Then I'm going with you.
Kate
Kate...
-发生什么了  Aaron在哪  -别问
What happened? where's aaron? where-- no, don't ask questions.
如果你想让我一起走
If you want me to go with you...
就别再问我这个问题 别再问起Aaron
You'll never ask me that question again. You will never ask me about aaron.
明白吗  Jack
Do you understand, jack?
明白了
Yes.
谢谢
Thank you.
早
Morning.
我给你煮了咖啡  那儿有橙汁
Uh, I made you some coffee, and there's orange juice.
你还是牛奶和两块糖吗
You still like milk and two sugars?
是的
Yeah, sure.
那些在岛上不适用
Those don't make much sense for the island.
你还是考虑徒步旅行靴吧
You might want to consider hiking boots.
那些都是我父亲的
Those were my father's.
当我去悉尼接回他的尸体时
When I went to pick up his body in sydney,
我父亲没有什么好鞋
My dad didn't have any nice shoes.
我母亲想我一回到洛杉矶 就进行葬礼
My mother wanted to have the funeral Soon as I landed back in l.a.
但是我想  谁会看他的脚呢
But I thought, who the hell's gonna see his feet?
然后我就带了这些白色老式网球鞋
And so i-i had these old white tennis shoes,
我只说句  给他穿上这双吧
And I just said, "use these. put these on him."
因为他对于我来说  不如一双漂亮的鞋子
'cause he wasn't worth a nice pair of shoes to me.
或者时间会带走这一切
Or the time it would take to go out and get 'em.
那为什么你不扔掉它们呢
So why don't you get rid of 'em?
为什么还留着一些让你伤心的东西呢
Why hold on to something that makes you feel sad?
去接吧
Go ahead.
我
I...
我们机场见  好吗
I'll see you at the airport, okay?
-你好  -你好  Jack  你在吗
-Hello? -hello, jack. are you there?
一切都还好吗
Yeah. yeah, what's u is everything all right?
听着  我们时间不够  我出车祸了
Listen, we don't have much time. I've been, uh... sidetracked,
我要你
And I need you
带上Locke的尸体去机场
To pick up locke's body and take it to the airport.
棺材在西蒙的卖肉铺
The coffin is at simon's butcher shop,
Grand和Hayes的街角
Corner of grand and hayes.
为什么  你怎么了
Why? wh-what's happened to you?
就这样做吧
Just do it. please.
你是Jill吗  Ben让我来的
Are you jill? ben sent me.
我知道你是谁  Shephard医生  进来吧
I know who you are, dr. shephard. come on in.
包里是什么
What's in the bag?
抱歉
Sorry.
Ben说把货车给你
Ben said to give you the van.
我把车开过来  等我5分钟
I gotta pull it around back. give me about five minutes.
不管你在哪  John
Wherever you are, john...
看到我在做的事
You must be laughing your ass off
你肯定要笑疯了
That I'm actually doing this.
因为这个
Because this...
这比你还疯狂
This is even crazier than you are.
还有这个
And here.
你可以拿回去
You can have that back.
你把一切都告诉我了  John
I've already heard everything you had to say, john.
你希望我回去  我就回去
You wanted me to go back. I'm going back.
安息吧
Rest in peace.
Shephard先生  我可以问一下
Mr. shephard, if you'll just bear with me.
你为什么把Bentham先生运到关岛吗
The reason for transporting mr. bentham to guam?
这是他的心愿
Uh, it was his-- these were his wishes.
他希望能埋葬在那儿
He wanted to be buried there.
到达以后谁会是接收者呢
Who will be the recipient of the deceased upon arrival?
没有  是我  我负责护送尸体
no, it's me. me. I'll be escorting the body.
你和死者的关系是什么
And your relation to the deceased?
他是我的朋友
He was, uh, a friend.
Shephard先生  我得告知你
Now, mr. shephard, I have to inform you that
因为保安措施加强  我们要求
Due to the increased security measures, we are required
打开棺材  检查一下
To open the casket and perform a screening.
我向你保证会非常小心的
I assure you it's all done with care.
你理解吗  Shephard先生
Do you understand, mr. shephard?
Shephard先生
Mr. shephard?
我理解
Yes. yes, I understand.
那请在这儿签名
Then please sign here.
感谢你选乘Ajira航空
Thank you for flying ajira air.
我表示哀悼
My condolences.
我对你失去朋友表示遗憾
I'm sorry you lost your friend.
谢谢
Thank you.
请把所有的上衣套衫
Please remove all jackets, sweaters,
珠宝和鞋袜都脱掉
Jewelry and footwear.
把笔记本拿出来
Remove all laptops
一切电子设备都从你们的行李里拿出来
And electronic devices from their cases
然后将它们放在
And place them...
Jack
Jack.
Sun  你好
Sun. hey.
见到我很惊讶吗
You're surprised to see me?
我只是
I just...
我以为你会改变想法
I thought maybe you might change your mind.
万一Jin还活着呢
If there's even a chance that jin is alive,
我必须要上飞机
I have to be on that plane.
所有乘客  在过安检时
All passengers, please have your tickets and identification
请将你们的机票和身份证都拿出来
Available for security.
请将所有的上衣套衫
Please remove all jackets, sweaters...
笔记本和电子设备
...all laptops and electronic devices
从你们的行李里取出  将他们放在箱子里
From their cases and place them in a bin.
这是Ajira航空公司3-1-6次航班
This is the preliminary boarding announcement
去往檀香山和关岛的
For ajira airways flight 3-1-6,
登机通知
With service to honolulu and guam,
请从15号门出发
Departing from gate 15.
在等候名单中的旅客
For those of you on the standby list,
我们还有少量的座位
We'll have plenty of seats available.
我们诚挚的邀请我们的前排
We would like to invite our pre-board, first class
头等舱和飞行会员乘客现在登机
And skyclub passengers to board the aircraft at this time.
等候名单是什么意思  这没有等候的啊
What do you mean "standby"? there's no standbys.
先生  你不用担心
oh, no, sir.You don't need to worry. there are...
还有78个座位是空着的
78 seats open.
不对  我买下了所有78个的座位
No. I bought those seats, all 78 of 'em.
我是Hugo Reyes  座位没有空位  都是我的
I'm hugo reyes. they're not open. they're mine.
你看看
Check and see.
是的  我看到了
Yes, I see that.
先生  那些乘客只是想到他们的目的地
Sir, these people just want to get to their destination.
为什么你不想让他们乘坐呢
Why would you not want them to be able to travel?
你知道的  没有任何原因 他们要坐下一班飞机
You know, it doesn't matter why. they can take the next plane.
Hurley
Hurley.
你在这儿干嘛  你怎么知道
What are you doing here? how did you know about the...
最重要的是我在这儿  对吗
All that matters is that I'm here, right?
我很高兴你在这儿  伙计
I'm glad that you're here, man.
那好吧
Okay, then.
我们走吧
Let's do this.
你先
After you.
欢迎乘坐Ajira航空客机
Welcome to Ajira Air.
谢谢  先生  第八排  在您的左手边
Thank you, sir. Row 8, on your left.
欢迎乘机
Welcome aboard.
是的  女士  可以  谢谢
Yes, ma'am. You may. Thank you.
不客气  请确保将你的...
Yes, make sure you put your...
我会的
I will.
绝对保证
Absolutely.
你来了
You made it.
是的
Yeah.
我来了
I made it.
-人都到齐了  - 别关门  请等等
- That should be everybody. - Hold up! Wait, please!
谢谢你没有关门
Thank you for not closing it.
-不客气  快进来吧  -谢谢
- Oh, that's okay. go right on in. - Thanks.
等等  他怎么来了
Wait! What's he doing here?!
-Hurley  -不  不  他不能来
- Hurley, hey-- - No, no! He can't come!
如果你想回去  就必须得这样
If you want to get back, this is how it's gonna have to be.
没人告诉我他也来
No one told me he was gonna be here.
谁告诉你来的  Hugo
Who told you to be here, Hugo?
一切都好吗
Is everything okay?
是的  一切都好
Yes. Yes, everything's fine.
-对吗  -是的  Jack  我没事
- Right? - Yes, Jack. I'll be fine.
你是Jack Shephad  坐8C位子的
Are you Jack Shephard, seat 8c?
是
Yes.
扫描你的行李的时候保安发现了这个
Security found this while screening your cargo.
如果你们两个好好坐下
Now if y two don't mind taking your seats,
我们要起飞了
We are gonna be pushing back for takeoff.
怎么了  Jack
What's that, jack?
没什么
Nothing.
这架飞机上的其他人
And the other people on this plane--
他们会怎么样
What's gonna happen to them?
谁在乎
Who cares?
这很疯狂  是吗
It's pretty crazy, huh?
哪儿疯狂
Which part?
Hurley  Sayid 在 同一架飞机上
Hurley, sayid... Being... On the same plane.
他们是怎么到那里的
How did they end up here?
他们买了一张票
They bought a ticket.
你不认为这说明了一些问题吗
You don't think that it means something?
不知怎么...
That somehow...
我们全部一起返回了吗
We're all back together?
我们在同一架飞机上  Jack
We're on the same plane, jack.
不表示我们在一起
Doesn't make us together.
下午好  女士们  先生们
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen,
欢迎乘坐Ajira航空班机
And welcome to Ajira air.
我是你们的机长  Frank J Lapidus
This is your captain, frank j. lapidus,
我代表全体机组成员  欢迎您乘坐
And on behalf of the entire flight crew, welcome aboard.
目前我们正点飞行
Currently we're right on schedule,
海拔高度30000英尺
Flying at a very comfortable 30,000 feet.
-打扰一下  女士  -Shephand先生  有什么需要帮忙
- Excuse me, ma'am? - Mr. shephard, can I help you?
我想跟飞行员讲句话
Um, I need to talk to the pilot.
Frank Lapidus和我是老朋友  如果你能
Frank lapidus and I are old friends, and if you could
告诉他我也在机上  我会非常感激
Just tell him I'm onboard, I'd really appreciate it.
好吧  但是请您坐下
All right, but you just have to go sit down
因为驾驶舱门打开的时候 你不能在附近
Because you can't be near the cockpit door When it's open. sure.
当然  我明白
I understand.
机长  有位乘客叫Jack Shephard
Captain, I have a passenger named Jack Shephard.
他说他认识您
He says he knows you. okay, sir.
你好啊  大夫
Well, hello, doc.
世界真小啊
Small world.
你去关岛干什么
What are you doing going to Guam?
你在这里做什么  Frank
What are you doing here, Frank?
大概8个月以前  我接手这架飞机
Well, I picked this gig up about eight months ago.
一直飞这个航线
I fly this route all the time.
有时  我会载人去新德里
Sometimes I take the big birds into New... Delhi.
是
Is...
那个Sayid吗
That Sayid?
还有Hurley
And Hurley.
等一下
Wait a second.
我们不是要去关岛  是吗
We're not going to Guam, are we?
你怎么看得进去书
How can you read?
我母亲教我的
My mother taught me.
我之所以要读书  Jack
I can read, jack,
是因为这能碍你的事
Because it beats what you're doing.
碍什么事  等待某些事发生
What's that? waiting for something to happen
会发生什么事
And what is gonna happen?
告诉我  Jack
You tell me, Jack.
是你要和Hawking小姐 放学后留下来
You're the one that got to stay After school with Ms. Hawking.
你知道Locke自杀了吗
Did you know that Locke killed himself?
不  我不知道
No. no, I didn't.
他们在他的口袋里找到了这个东西
They found this stuffed in his pocket.
我曾试图摆脱它,但是好像它...
And I've been trying to get rid of it, But it's like it's...
一直跟着我
Following me.
我知道这听上去很疯狂  但是
I know it sounds crazy, but...
好像John需要我读这个
It feels like John needs me to read it.
那你为什么不读
Why don't you then?
是因为害怕吗
Is it because you're afraid?
怕什么
Afraid of what?
害怕他责备你
Afraid that he blames you,
他自杀是你的错
That it's your fault he killed himself.
是我的错吗
Was it my fault?
不  Jack  不是你的错
No, Jack, it wasn't your fault.
我让你自己待会儿
Let me give you some privacy.
Jack  我希望你当时相信了我
Jack, I wish you had believed me
伙计
Dude...
你也许需要扣紧安全带
You might wanna fasten your seat belt.
扣紧你的安全带  女士  先生
Fasten your seat belt, ma'am. sir?
请扣好安全带  请扣安全带
Please put on your seat belts. seat belt, please.
救命
Help!
来人啊
Anyone!
救命
Help!
Kate
Kate.
怎么啦
What happened?
-你能起来吗  -能
- Can you get up? - yeah.
飞机
The plane...
飞机去哪儿了
Where's the plane?
我不知道
I don't know.
亮光闪过以后  我
After that light, i...
我醒来就在丛林里
I woke up in the jungle.
那么就是这样啦  只有我们
So this is it? it's just us?
不好说
I'm not sure.
你们有人记得发生坠机吗
Do either of you remember crashing?
坠机  没有  一下子  我被抛了起来
Crashing? no. one second, I'm being tossed around.
接下来就发现  我在湖里
The next thing I know, I'm in the lagoon.
Sun和Sayid在哪儿
Where's Sun and Sayid?
Ben在哪儿
Where's Ben?
好了  我们分散开  搜索丛林
All right. let's spread out, search the jungle.
如果碰到飞机上的任何一人  我们就
We come across anybody from the plane, we'll--
伙计
Dude...
Jin
Jin?